<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>nem4ros</title>
    <link>https://cryogas.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on nem4ros</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>© nem4ros</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 29 Sep 2024 15:10:12 +0800</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://cryogas.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>IBOH 2024 Writeup</title>
      <link>https://cryogas.github.io/content/iboh24/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Sep 2024 15:10:12 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>https://cryogas.github.io/content/iboh24/</guid>
      <description>Introduction The annual main event of CTF in Asia Pacific University (APU): International Battle of Hackers, hosted by FSEC-CC, with amazing CTF players from not only Malaysia, but other countries such as Singapore and Indonesia participating.&#xA;The challenges were difficult in my opinion, and most of them were removed after the event, therefore I did not manage to screenshot the solution for most of them.&#xA;Therefore, here is my humble writeup for one of the crypto challenge: I&amp;rsquo;ll Kill Yall.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title> FSIIEC CTF Writeup</title>
      <link>https://cryogas.github.io/content/fsiiecctf24/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Sep 2024 21:50:02 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>https://cryogas.github.io/content/fsiiecctf24/</guid>
      <description>Introduction This is my writeup for FSIIEC CTF.&#xA;Boss Password An obfuscated passage is given.&#xA;To deobfuscate the passage, look at the hint closely&amp;hellip; Hint The hint obviosuly states the key is &amp;ldquo;to be as sneaky as possible&amp;rdquo;&#xA;Just take the message literally and use it as a key to decode the message and convert the message to MD5 hash. Solved! Kagegakure To solve this challenge, I used curl -L command on Linux (Ubuntu) to read all the contents on the website.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DownUnderCTF24 Writeup</title>
      <link>https://cryogas.github.io/content/ductf24/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Jul 2024 09:13:25 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>https://cryogas.github.io/content/ductf24/</guid>
      <description>💡 DownUnderCTF, the Largest CTF in the Southern Hemisphere!&#xD;The challenges in this CTF are hard! But I managed to solve some of the easier challenges, so here is my writeup for DownUnderCTF!&#xA;MISC Discord The challenge requires us to get the flag in Discord server.&#xA;To do this, we just search for &amp;ldquo;DUCTF&amp;rdquo; in the Discord chat.&#xA;Found Part 1 Looking around for some time, but could&amp;rsquo;nt find the second part.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UIUCTF 2024 Writeup</title>
      <link>https://cryogas.github.io/content/uiuctf24/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://cryogas.github.io/content/uiuctf24/</guid>
      <description>💡 UIUCTF2024, hosted by SIGPwny, the cybersecurity club at the University of Illinois Urbana-Champaign (UIUC).&#xD;For this CTF competition, I am only able to do some OSINT challenges, so here is my writeup for UIUCTF2024!&#xA;OSINT Hip With the Youth This challenge requires players to find the flag on the social media of Long Island Subway Authority (LISA).&#xA;From the Instagram account, there are no flags visible.&#xA;Lisa&amp;#39;s Instagram Account After looking through the posts and followers list, nothing useful is found.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wani Ctf 2024 Writeup</title>
      <link>https://cryogas.github.io/content/wani-ctf/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 23:15:36 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>https://cryogas.github.io/content/wani-ctf/</guid>
      <description>This is my writeup for Wani CTF, an event organized by Osaka University CTF Club, Wani Hackase (Rank 304th)&#xA;Forensics Surveillance of sus A binary file is given, and after some investigation, it has a RDP8BMP Header.&#xA;To get the BMP images, I have referred to this article and use a Python Script (bmc-tools).&#xA;After all the bmp files are recovered, the flag can be readed in plain sight if the view is changed to &amp;ldquo;Large icons&amp;rdquo;.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VSCTF Awa-Jelly Writeup</title>
      <link>https://cryogas.github.io/content/vsctf/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Jun 2024 11:32:57 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>https://cryogas.github.io/content/vsctf/</guid>
      <description>For this CTF, I only solved one question by myself, so here is the writeup for awa-jelly (reverse engineering)&#xA;Basically, the challenge is to recover the redacted input text so that the output is same as displayed.&#xA;Although I know Python a little, I decided to use the traditional method: Excel 🤦🏻&#xA;Throughout my process, I tried to recover the scrambling algorithm by using Python, and I discovered some characters cannot be displayed after scrambling, which caused my natural approach to be weird due to some characters are missing.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://cryogas.github.io/about/this/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://cryogas.github.io/about/this/</guid>
      <description>Name: nem4ros</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
